snakesonacane.com 2012-06-06

# FOX Broadcasting Company - FOX Network Sites Terms of Use

Effective April 23, 2012:

Summary of the FOX Privacy Policy:

  1. **INTRODUCTION** \- The Introduction identifies the basic FOX Services covered by this Privacy Policy and provides a brief overview of what this Privacy Policy covers. 
  2. **SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION** \- This section addresses the types of information that FOX collects directly from users and the collection of information via cookies and related technologies by, and on behalf of, FOX and third parties.
  3. **NOTICE AND CHOICE** \- This section provides information on users' options to control how their information is collected and used, how FOX notifies users about future Privacy Policy changes, where FOX stores data, and third party websites that may link to the Services.
  4. **USE AND DISCLOSURE** \- This section describes how FOX uses your information to provide and manage the FOX Services, including when FOX may disclose your information to third parties that assist FOX in providing those services. 
  5. **SECURITY** \- This section describes FOX's security measures. 
  6. **USER CONTROL AND ACCOUNT CANCELLATION** \- This section informs users how to access and change their personal information stored by FOX, and how to cancel their accounts.
  7. **CONTACT US** \- This section instructs users how to contact FOX.

* * *

## 1\. INTRODUCTION

FOX Broadcasting Company ("FOX" or "we") operates FOX.com and other FOX show and entertainment websites that are operated by FOX (collectively, the "FOX Website" or "Site"). The services FOX offers include the FOX Websites, applications (in connection with the Site or third party services), community pages and any other features, content, promotions, games or applications offered from time to time by FOX including when accessed via the Internet, mobile or other devices (collectively, the "FOX Services"). FOX is part of the United States based operations of News Corporation.

As set forth in our Terms of Use, the FOX Services are for a general audience, are not targeted to children, and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

This Privacy Policy applies to all "users," including both those who use a FOX Service without being registered with FOX or subscribing to a FOX Service and those who have registered with or subscribed to any FOX Service. This Privacy Policy describes FOX's collection and use of users' personal information (e.g., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address) where that information is not otherwise publicly available on the FOX Services. We also provide information on the FOX Privacy Settings and describe generally FOX's practices for handling non-personally identifiable information (e.g., interests, demographics and site usage) to the extent such information is associated with a particular user or user account.

## 2\. SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION ON THE FOX SERVICES

_User Submitted Information_

**Account Information** is the information that users provide to FOX when they register for or subscribe to a FOX Service, for example, to create an account or profile, enter a contest or sweepstakes, receive a newsletter, play a game or take a survey. This information may include, for example, name, display name, email address, gender, location, and date of birth. If you create a profile in connection with any of the FOX Services, your profile information may also be publicly available to anyone, unless the FOX Service for which you create the profile provides Privacy Settings to allow you to control the parties with whom you share that content.

**Public Information and Posts** consist of your display name and, if you provide one, your profile picture and your posts and comments on or in connection with the FOX Services. Your Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and can be displayed in search results.

**Third Party Information and Content.** If you access a FOX Service through a third party connection or log-in or connect a FOX Service to a third party service, your user submitted information may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that third party service, any information/content you have permitted the third party to share with FOX, and any information you have made public in connection with that third party service (collectively, "Third Party Information and Content"). Depending on what information you have submitted to the third party service, this may include, for instance, your name, email address, self-declared location, profile picture, gender, date of birth and hometown. When you access a FOX Service through a third party service or log-in or connect a FOX Service to a third party service, you are authorizing FOX to collect, store, and use, in accordance with this Privacy Policy, any and all Third Party Information and Content.

_FOX Collected Information_

**Transactional and Site Activity Information.** When users access the FOX Services, we collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the FOX Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the FOX Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it. We may also use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe flash technology), which are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that site. These technologies may be used to collect and store information about your usage of the FOX Services, such as pages you have visited, search queries you have run, and advertisements you have seen. FOX may also use cookies, pixels and similar tools to relate your use of the FOX Services to personal information obtained from you, from publicly available sources or a reputable third party. For example, if you have asked us to provide you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on the FOX Websites may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences.

Third parties that support the FOX Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as providing users with the ability to comment on content, allowing users to share content or tracking aggregate site usage statistics may also use these technologies to collect similar information. FOX does not control these third party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of these third parties using such technologies. For more information about third party ad networks and services that use these technologies, see [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/), and to opt out of such ad networks' and services' collection and advertising practices, go to [aboutads.info/choices](http://aboutads.info/choices). 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information (e.g., http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies). Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the [Flash management tools available at Adobe's website](http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html). Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features or personalization available through the FOX Services.

**Third Parties.** To improve the quality of our services, FOX may supplement the information we collect with information we obtain from third parties or from publicly available sources. If you access a FOX Service through a third party connection or log-in or connect a FOX Service to a third party service, we may also collect Third Party Information and Content and combine that Third Party Information and Content with your Account Information and information we obtain from third parties or from publicly available sources. 

## 3\. NOTICE & CHOICE

**Means of Notice and Choice.** This Privacy Policy and your Privacy Settings are the primary means by which FOX provides you with notice and choice about its collection and use of your personal information. FOX will not use your personal information in a manner different from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your permission.

**Privacy Policy Changes.** FOX may modify this Privacy Policy as necessary. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that expand our rights to use your personal information, we will notify you to seek your consent either through an email or a prominent posting at our FOX Services. In the event the last email address you provided to FOX is not valid or is not capable of delivering the notice to you, FOX's dispatch of an email containing the notice to that email address shall nonetheless constitute effective notice.

**Location of Data Storage.** The FOX Services are hosted in the United States. If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to and processed in the United States and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may be different than those in your jurisdiction, such as the laws of the European Union. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

**Linked Services.** FOX Services may also be linked to sites or services operated by FOX affiliates (i.e., that are part of News Corporation) ("Affiliated Companies") or third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, rewards programs, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by third parties including, the online store. FOX is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave FOX Services via a link, enable a third party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. Additionally, although all Affiliated Companies adhere to the News Corporation corporate [Privacy Principles](http://www.newscorp.com/privacy.html), users who visit an Affiliated Company site should still refer to its separate privacy policy, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy. [Click here to see a list of the News Corporation Affiliated Companies](http://www.newscorp.com/).

**California Residents.** If you are a California resident, you may request that we do not share your personal information on a going-forward basis with third parties for their direct marketing purposes by sending an email to [californiaprivacy@fox.com](mailto:californiaprivacy@fox.com?subject=Fox.com:%20Disclosure%20Opt-out), with "Fox.com: Disclosure Opt-out" in the subject line and your full name, email address, and postal address in the body of the email.

## 4\. USE & DISCLOSURE

_Information Made Public Through Use of FOX Services and User Privacy Settings_

If you create a profile in connection with any of the FOX Services, your profile information may also be publicly available to anyone, unless the FOX Service for which you create the profile provides Privacy Settings to allow you to control which parties with whom you share that content. Users' Public Information and Posts are always publicly available to anyone, including other users, search engines, advertisers, third party application developers, and anyone else with access to the FOX Services.

_FOX's Use and Disclosure of Information_

FOX may share your personal information with Affiliated Companies. We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy.

We use the information we collect from and about users for the following purposes:

**To provide and manage the FOX Services.** We use the information we collect from and about users to provide the FOX Services and features to you, including to measure and improve those services and features, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising and marketing messages, to allow you to comment on content, participate in online games, contests, promotions or rewards programs, to enable you to communicate and share with other people or services, and to provide you with customer support and respond to inquiries. We may also use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on the FOX Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

**To allow third party service providers to assist us in providing and managing the FOX Services.** FOX may make your non-public personal information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide FOX Services by, for example: developing or supporting products and features; conducting email marketing on our behalf; processing payments; administering message boards; fulfilling orders; processing data or statistics; or assisting with the administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions and sweepstakes. These outside service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to FOX.

**To contact you.** FOX may periodically send promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications to the email address you provided to us at registration or subscription to your account. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from FOX, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of as long as you are registered with or subscribed to the FOX Services, such as notifications of changes to the FOX Services or policies. 

**To allow other users to find you.** In order to locate other users that a user may already know in the physical world and/or want to get to know in the online world, the FOX Services may allow users to search for other users using information the user already knows, such as name, display name or email address. 

**To deliver relevant advertising.** We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of the FOX Services through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you visit the FOX Services or other websites. We may work with third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. We do not share your non-public personal information with these third parties, but we may share de-identified, anonymized or aggregated information with them to improve the relevancy of the ads you see on the FOX Services. As noted above, these third party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about third party online advertising and to opt out of this type of advertising, visit [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**To protect the rights of FOX and our users.** There may be instances when FOX may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where FOX has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety or property of FOX and our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy and security of users of the FOX Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process; and (v) respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence.

**To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If FOX sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, FOX may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

## 5\. SECURITY

FOX uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard user information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. If you are asked to select a password to access a FOX Service, you should select a password that contains a combination of letters, numbers and non-alphanumeric characters (for example, %, $ and &) and avoid dictionary words. In addition, you should not use the same password that you use for other business or personal accounts.

## 6\. USER CONTROL AND ACCOUNT CANCELLATION

Through your "Edit Your FOX Profile" settings, you can access, edit or delete information that you have provided to FOX for your Fox.com profile. You also can link or unlink your FOX profile from third party service accounts under the "Linked Accounts" heading on your "Edit Your FOX Profile" page, or by unlinking your FOX profile through your account on the third party service. If you no longer want to use the FOX Services, you may cancel your account by clicking on "Delete Profile" on your "Edit Your FOX Profile" page. You may unsubscribe to the FOX newsletter by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the newsletter email.

Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in circumstances where, for example, you have posted information on another user's profile, shared information with a third party application or website, or if another person copied, stored or shared your information. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancellation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others, and there may be a delay in the removal of the content from elsewhere on the Internet and from search engines.

## 7\. CONTACT US

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact FOX by emailing [privacy@fox.com](mailto:privacy@fox.com). Or, you can contact us by mail at:

Privacy Officer  
10201 West Pico Boulevard  
Bldg. 100, 3220  
Los Angeles, CA 90035
